What's this? A tongue twister?
Please, no!
Leave the tongue twister to me.
Thanks! You're a lifesaver!
It's got a lot of big words, though.
This is a message from Apollo.
Ugh!
Okay, take turns and let's keep going.
By streaming this, she's telling me
she's in the broadcast club.
Okay!
This is from "Love You All."
So why?
Why won't she reveal herself?
Thanks for writing in!
"I'd like to know how to join
the Shinobu-chan fanclub," they say.
Hey, wait! There's no such thing!
BROADCASTING ROOM (TEMP)
Sure there is.
And boys aren't allowed to join.
I wouldn't do that.
Oh, so boys are welcome, too?
Huh? Uh...
Urk...
Hide all you want. I'll just find you.
And then...
I'll fulfill our promise.
Yeah! Peaceful is best!
I'll make professionals out of you all!
That's our vice prez for you.
Way to wrap up the topic.
ARISU: I'LL FULFILL OUR PROMISE.
I'LL MAKE PROFESSIONALS OUT OF YOU ALL!
Give me a break!
A healthy voice dwells in a healthy body!
These early morning runs should help
your voices advance to the next level!
Okay, but 6 AM is way too early! Jerk!
I want ice cream...
Hey, that seagull
has something in its beak.
My word!
Is that the earbud I lost yesterday?!
How are you faster than all of us
in reverse? That's freaky!
Well done!
That should do it for the warmup.
My heart's about to explode!
Oh? An irregular pulse?
A rapid heartbeat can be caused by
nerves or excitement, you know?
How the heck is he perfectly fine?
Wait, never mind that!
Why are you acting like our coach?!
Are you serious about making us pros?
I have never not been serious.
Rest assured. I am the very definition
of a man of his word.
Drop the smug act!
Now, now, Nene-chan.
It's true that we've been slacking off.
And we did talk about exercising,
so this works out perfectly.
Isn't that why you're here, Nene?
You sure talk a big game, though.
Why're you so set on making us pros?
Is it really just
your perfectionist nature talking?
Can we really trust you?
Of course. I am the rising tide
that will lift all your boats.
How about you back up
your claim, errand boy?
Gladly, but before that...
breakfast comes first.
Huh?
We're going to a restaurant.
N-Not sure that's the best idea...
I-I want to stop by our club room first.
Me, too.
What's with you all?
Why are you running away?
You moron!
We're all sweaty, so we wanna change!
Have a look.
TRAINING REGIMEN - UZUKI SHINOBU
What are these?
They detail your issues
as well as training regimens to fix them.
I've also listed reference materials
and works that might help.
They're all perfectly tailored
to each of you.
Take a look and marvel at
the depth of my knowledge.
Wow, this is really detailed.
Why am I the only one with a huge pile?!
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL KANJI
Because kanji drills.
You need to get better with them first.
It says my goal is to take
a VTuber agency audition.
Oh, and mine's to complete
an Anchor 101 course.
Mine's to pass the Level 3
Kanji Aptitude Test?!
And you, Rikka?
Sell 50 copies of my own CD
at a street performance.
Indeed. It's a good way to gain
confidence and experience, right?
What's the matter?
Say, Yamabuki-kun.
Have you ever played an instrument?
Never.
But if I stretch the definition a little,
I do enjoy whistling after a bath.
That's one hell of a stretch.
Do you have any idea
how much courage it takes
to play and sing in front of a crowd?
I don't, but it's a bridge you'll
have to cross if you want to go pro.
ROAD TO BECOMING A SINGER
ULTIMATE GOAL: CHART ON THE BILLBOARD
Surely you've felt your hands
shake from nerves, at least?
Never. Nervousness is not
in a Yamabuki's dictionary.
You've never been nervous in your life?
Liar.
You're all talk.
"All talk"?
I don't see why I should listen to you.
Wha? H-Hey!
Hoo boy, he made her mad.
Off with his head, I say.
Excuse me! I'd like an ice cream!
What's gotten into Inohana?
She's mad, and rightfully so.
She's good enough to write her own songs,
but some jerk who's all talk—
who can't even read sheet music—
thinks he can order her around.
Stop it, Nene-chan.
Don't kick him when he's down.
What? I'm just stating facts.
Huh?
Bucky's gone.
A... All talk?
Who, yours truly?
Whoa, you brought him to his knees!
What a massive insult.
Nobody has ever said that to me!
Only my big sis, little sis, and mother!
That's quite the list.
She must be an amazing musician
to have the gall to say I'm all talk!
I need to hear for myself
just how good she is.
Bye!
I'm starving!
Inohana Rikka does mini-concerts
every Wednesday after school.
She performs in the school courtyard.
Her female fans camp out there,
making it hard for boys to watch.
Thanks for joining me again this week!
Th-This is a bigger audience
than I expected!
Huh?
There's a boy here!
Keep your skeevy eyes off our Rikka-chan!
Wait! I'm a member
of the broadcasting club!
This still makes me nervous every time.
I wonder if you all can tell.
WAITING FOR THE STREAM TO BEGIN...
This still makes me nervous every time.
APOLLO HAS STARTED STREAMING
"MIDNIGHT HEART TUNE"
I wonder if you can tell.
Sorry if I miss a few notes, okay?
Whoa, yeah
Ah, when did I start yearning for a goal?
I was happy just walking down my path
I hear voices telling me I can't do it
But I keep going with my head held high
Because burning deep inside of me
Is a dazzling light, a soaring heartbeat
They never let me forget
I run, and I run
As my heart wills me to
And I write, and I write
My tell-all life story
I break, and I break through
All the walls fate puts before me
I crumble, and I fall
But I still reach out for what lies ahead
That's my own personal theory
That was awesome!
When I heard Inohana sing,
I saw a glimpse of Apollo.
The next song will be my last.
If you don't have any requests,
I guess I could—
Play that new KinFri song!
Me, too!
NEW SONGS - LYRICS 2 FOR CONCERTS
I love the dance!
Can you do that one, Rikka-chan?
Yeah, of course.
Why'd you have to come?
I didn't want you listening to my songs.
FURIN HIGH SCHOOL
Thank you!
Bye.
Can't wait for next week.
Hey...
If it isn't Mr. All-Talk.
Stop calling me that!
You came to hear me sing, huh?
Well? Is your heart mine now?
Yes, that was incredible!
You took my breath away!
Allow me to apologize!
I have no doubt that your
street performance will be a hit!
Kiss my ass all you want,
but I'm still not going to do as you say.
See ya!
Yamabuki-kun's stopped coming to watch me.
He hasn't been showing up
for club, either.
I guess I went too far.
I should apologize when I see him.
Give us Rikka-chan!
We're not here for you!
Get lost!
Thank you all for coming to see
yours truly's first-ever concert!
Screw you!
Nobody came to see your sorry ass!
You suck!
Sell your guitar!
Tough crowd, much?
I've only played one song!
Hey, Inohana. Long time no see.
What are you doing?
Putting on a show, that's what.
Remember what you said?
You said that I was all talk.
That's why I secretly worked
on my guitar and vocal skills...
All to prove you wrong!
Prove me wrong?
You learned to play
the guitar just for that?
Mhm!
Sheesh.
You're crazy.
Sorry!
I forgot to tell you all that
I'll be performing with him today.
Huh? What the heck?
Wha? How's that going to work?
Don't worry about it.
Play however you like. I'll back you up.
O-O...kay? Okay!
Way to make a mess out of my show.
My apologies.
So, how was it?
You had to have been nervous.
Was your heart pounding?
Like I said before, I don't get nervous.
Yours truly has seen
not just some, but all the shit.
I've got nothing but ice in my veins.
There you go again.
You sure about that?
Sure as the sun rises.
Uh-huh...
Whoa! What are you doing?!
LIAR.
I'm heading out. I've got plans again.
You've sure been busy lately.
Someone's up to no good.
And someone's wrong as hell.
Hold it.
At this rate, passing the Level 3 Kanji
Aptitude Test will remain a pipe dream.
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL KANJI
That's your dream, not mine!
Nene-chan's been
kind of a stranger lately.
Those were the eyes of
a girl with something to hide.
She must be up to no good,
like Kirino said.
Oh, you don't have to worry about that.
How can you be sure, Uzuki?
I mean, it's super obvious.
When Nene-chan's lying...
I know what Uzuki said,
but I'm not so sure.
"I'm sorry for summoning you here."
She's practicing in secret?
A soft, pleasant voice, much like
a cat that wants some love.
"Before you leave me,
It really does feel familiar.
there is something I must tell you."
However...
However, I say!
Your acting downright sucks!
E-Eek!
Can you try to put some emotion into it?!
It's nothing like what I heard
from you before!
Don't spy on me, you freak!
"Knightly Love"?
Don't you know?
It's the hottest manga right now.
KNIGHTLY LOVE
Knightly Love.
A tale of forbidden love between princess
and soldier, and it's got all the feels.
The princess rushes
to the fallen soldier's side.
How she wants to hold him, but
nobody can find out about their romance.
So she pretends to brush
the dirt off him...
and secretly plants a kiss on his helmet!
Is this what you're into, Himekawa?
Dude, your face!
Admiring my flawless
complexion, are we?
I meant it was too close, dumbass!
KNIGHTLY LOVE: ANIME ADAPTATION CONFIRMED!
AUDITIONS FOR PRINCESS ROLE OPEN!
An audition?
Get out. I need to practice.
You're trying out?
It's not any of your business.
Stay out of it.
Oh, but it is, so I'm staying right here.
I promised to make you
all pros, after all.
Well, I didn't ask you to.
I'll have you know I wet my bed
during my middle school trip.
Wha?
I've also wet myself
from pain at the dentist.
Why are you sharing this?!
I've also been scolded for overfilling
the containers for urine tests!
Just how messed up is your bladder, dude?!
If you're embarrassed,
I'll be embarrassed with you.
Well? Feel like speaking up now?
I am trying out.
It's just, I've never...
Huh?
It's just, I've never been
in a relationship.
I don't know how to act out
a confession scene.
What, that's it?
I'm being serious here!
"If you lack experience,
go out and get some."
That's Yamabuki Family Tenet Number 23.
Nene...
Let's be lovers.
Wha?!
Wh-Wh-Wh-What are you saying?!
The line from the scene where
the soldier asks the princess out.
Starting today, I'm the soldier
and you're the princess.
Act as my lover until the audition
to get used to the role.
I'd rather die!
When is the audition?
In three weeks, why?
Oh, yeah? So, in your eyes,
your dream's not even worth keeping up
a pretense for a mere three weeks.
All that love you showed the manga
earlier must've been fake, too.
DAY 1 AS LOVERS
Nene-chan has a boyfriend?!
Yamabuki!
Ugh, look at that punchable face!
But she said she had no time for love!
A breeze most pleasant,
wouldn't you say, my princess?
Y-Y-Y-Ye-Yes, I suppose.
Oh, dear!
Are you all right, my princess?
Huh? I'm fine?
Your heels are broken.
I'll give you a ride on my back.
This guy...
He's copying the manga beat for beat!
Is he gonna act out the story
for three whole weeks?
Huh? Wait, the manga's
final chapter has...
Is he planning to do the kiss scene, too?!
DAY 3 AS LOVERS
BROADCASTING ROOM (TEMP)
What the heck?
You two were an item?
Your faces are sheer horror.
Okay, say, "Aah."
Aah.
DAY 10 AS LOVERS
How beautiful the moon is tonight.
All I see are clouds.
DAY 15 AS LOVERS
Whoa, slow down!
DAY 19 AS LOVERS
Hey, I'm wearing a skirt, you know?
So was the princess in the manga.
It's all right.
You're not heavy at all, my princess!
That line's not in the manga!
They're sure not acting like lovers.
If anything, they're bickering more.
Why can't you put more heart into it?!
Because I have to look
at your stupid face!
Now, now. It just shows...
how much closer they've gotten now, no?
DAY 20 AS LOVERS
The audition is tomorrow.
We've perfectly acted out the manga's
story over these three weeks.
So, do you have a better
understanding of the role now?
Don't ask me.
We did pretty much all the events
the princess experienced.
The boat ride, the feeding scene,
and the princess carry...
All that's left is
the final chapter's k-k...
Kiss!
The way this is going,
we might just kiss for real!
What do I do?
My lips are all chapped right now!
Wait, was the coaching just an excuse?
He just wanted to kiss me all along?
Ugh, disgusting. Why are boys like this?
I don't think we missed anything...
Nah, even I can tell that's not true.
He was seriously trying to help me.
He read the manga more than me
and played the role
of the soldier to perfection.
My acting has gotten way better, too.
All right. Now you just need...
Yep, called it. "Now you just need
to practice the kiss," right?
I'm not happy about it,
but practice is practice.
Himekawa.
Now you just need to rest up
before the audition.
What?!
We're not practicing the kiss scene?!
Obviously not.
But you were so into the lovers thing!
Save that kind of thing for someone
you're actually in love with.
Stupid! You'll regret this forever!
I am not stupid.
I got top scores on my exams.
You stupid idiot!
Hey, Himekawa.
Believe in yourself.
I know you'll ace the audition.
It was just a tiny bit, okay?
These past three weeks...
I may have had
the tiniest bit of fun, okay?!
Glad to hear it. Good luck.
I got rejected.
Why? My program was perfect!
They're saying online that
the author handpicked his favorite.
That's not fair...
No, I should've seen it coming.
Forgive me!
If only I had more foresight...
The princess rushes
to the fallen soldier's side.
How she wants to hold him,
but nobody can find out
about their romance.
So she pretends to
brush the dirt off him...
and secretly plants
a kiss on his helmet.
Hmm? Did you do something just now?
Not really.
I'm heading out, okay?
No, wait.
You just kissed me, didn't you?
I could tell from
your breathing and posture.
I'm guessing you reenacted that scene
you said had all the feels?
I apologize if I'm mistaken,
but Himekawa...
Are you in love with me?
And here I was trying
to make you feel better.
Get over yourself, you dumbass!
I hate you!
Whoa.
Wh-What's wrong?
Yamabuki-kun?
What could've possibly brought
a boy down to one knee in here?
Did you miss a penalty kick or something?
Y-Yours truly is now a hated man,
and it's all down to my hubris!
Huh...
Well, I'm pretty sure
the "I hate you" was a lie.
Remember what I told you before?
It's super obvious.
When Nene-chan's lying...
HIMEKAWA NENE'S EARS GIVE IT AWAY.
Translation:
Timing:
Editing:
Sriram Gurunathan
Mariana Martinez
William Haggard
Quality Check:
Translation Check:
S Bilyeu
Michelle Tymon